Based on the true story of a marine's best friend.
Megan Leavey is a drama, war film directed by Gabriela Cowperthwaite.
The true story of Marine Corporal Megan Leavey, who forms a
powerful bond with an aggressive combat dog, Rex.
While deployed in Iraq, the two complete more than 100 missions and save countless
lives, until an IED explosion puts their faithfulness to the test.
Megan Leavey, played by Kate Mara.
Matt Morales, played by Ramón Rodríguez.
Sergeant Andrew Dean, played by Tom Felton.
Bob, played by Bradley Whitford.
Jim, played by Will Patton.
Sills, played by Sam Keeley.
Megan Leavey (also known as Rex) is a 2017 American biographical drama film directed by Gabriela Cowperthwaite and written by Pamela Gray,
Annie Mumolo, and Tim Lovestedt, based on the true events about a young Marine named Megan Leavey and a combat dog named Rex.
The film stars Kate Mara as the titular character, with Edie Falco,
Common, Ramón Rodríguez, and Tom Felton in supporting roles.
The film was released on June 9, 2017, by Bleecker Street,
received positive reviews and grossed $14 million.
The film explores themes of human animal relationship, biography,
based on true story, iraq war veteran, female soldier.
The tone is emotional.